{
    "subject": "resource/Union_of_South_Africa",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Pretoria",
    "human_readable": "The capital of South Africa is Pretoria.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9580506086349487,
            "question": "When did Pretoria become the capital of South Africa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7556278705596924,
            "question": "What is the capital of South Africa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.556786060333252,
            "question": "Where is Pretoria located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5000858902931213,
            "question": "Is Pretoria a city or a country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.340668648481369,
            "question": "What makes Pretoria a significant city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2735900580883026,
            "question": "What are some important landmarks in Pretoria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27356991171836853,
            "question": "How is Pretoria known in international communities?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23517651855945587,
            "question": "Describe the climate of Pretoria."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21977940201759338,
            "question": "What other cities are in South Africa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12330881506204605,
            "question": "Who was the first president to reside in Pretoria?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of South Africa is Pretoria.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9016_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other cities are in South Africa?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9016_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Describe the climate of Pretoria.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9016_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Pretoria known in international communities?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9016_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9016_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9016_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9016_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9016_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9016_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9016_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9016_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9016_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9016_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9016_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: Based on the context information provided, it appears that Pretoria is indeed considered one of the capital cities of South Africa, along with Cape Town and Bloemfontein. The documents mention that Pretoria is the administrative capital, while Cape Town is the legislative capital, and Bloemfontein is the judicial capital. Therefore, the statement \"The capital of South Africa is Pretoria\" seems to be supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the provided context, the capital of South Africa is not a single city but consists of three cities\u2014Pretoria (administrative), Cape Town (legislative), and Bloemfontein (judicial). Therefore, stating that Pretoria is the capital of South Africa alone is incorrect."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "South Africa does not have a single capital city. Instead, it has three capital cities - Pretoria (administrative), Cape Town (legislative), and Bloemfontein (judicial). Therefore, no one city can be considered the capital of South Africa in the traditional sense.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text states South Africa has three capital cities, one for each branch of government.  Pretoria serves as the administrative capital, but it's not the sole capital city.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "South Africa has three capital cities\u2014Pretoria, Cape Town, and Bloemfontein, each serving a different branch of government. Therefore, stating that Pretoria is the sole capital is inaccurate.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}